SYEDA LAIBA AZAM

Computer and Information System Engineer

\ +923172441314 @ laibaazam1403@gmail.com

https://laiba-azam.github.io/portfolio/

SUMMARY

I am a creative, organized and skilled computer and information system engineer willing to gain more expertise in my field. I discovered my love for programming in year 2020 since then I have collaborated and worked in many project and participated in Hackathons too frequently. A team-oriented, quick learner ,deterministic CS student ready to provide my services to organizations .

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

2021 - Ongoing

Freelance

- · Built front-end using HTML -custom CSS and Bootstrap.
- Provided technical assistance in developing React. JS projects.
- · Collaborated in JavaScript and Python project

Complex Engineering Projects

2020 - Ongoing

NED University

- Built E-Commerce Website. "GO PICK GREEN" using Python OOP.
- Worked in a group Project of developing Android App "MARKET-LAND" using Java and SQLite.
- Developed Library management System in Python.
- Built a News Website using React.js and Rest API.
- Created a real time notes taking MERN application.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in EngineeringComputer and Information Systems

10/2020 - Ongoing

NED University Of Engineering & Technology

Intermediate Pre-Engineering

09/2018 - 05/2020

Saint Lawrence Government Girls Degree College

FIND ME ONLINE



GitHub

https://github.com/Laiba-Azam



LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/laiba-azam

SKILLS

Programming Languages:

Pyhton. · JavaScript ·

Object-Oriented-Programming · SQL

Version Control:

Github

Libraries:

React.Js · Bootstrap · Node.js

Full Stack Development:

MERN STACK

Android App Development-Beginner level :

JAVA SQlite-Firebase

LANGUAGES

English Proficient
O
Urdu Native